shmtranslations.com 2017-11-02

# Privacy Policy – SHMTranslations

**Privacy Policy**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This document outlines our privacy guidelines, to which you agree by navigating this site. Regular updates of the privacy policy are completed, requiring you to check back on this policy from time to time.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, this site makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**  
This site uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Personal Information**  
**This site does not require any personal information such as age, gender, location, etc. and will never ask for such informations**. While you are free to disclose this information yourself, posting personal information on the internet is strongly discouraged.

If you have any questions, please free to contact us at: Elite4Harmon@googlemail.com
